[Music]
I like the way that your body move all
over the floor nah nah nah I'd like to
find a way to get lost in you yeah yeah
yeah I want to talk to you baby say
what's on your
mind girl tell me anything that you want
to do yeah yeah yeah we all just looking
for some love in a night got a crazy
feeling that I fit you just right so try
me in the morning when the sun comes
rising up try me in the afternoon but
you just can't get enough try me in the
evening satisfaction guaranteed maybe I
got what you need you got to try me
[Music]
try
me talk to me let's go and find a place
and get to know each other more n n it's
all on your face I know you like what
you see yeah yeah yeah I'm the one for
you baby but you can take your time take
my time let the music bring your body to
me yeah yeah yeah we are just looking
for some love in the night looking for
got a crazy feeling that I F you just
right so try me in the morning when the
sun comes rising up try me in the
afternoon but you just can't get enough
try me in the EA satisfaction guaranteed
baby I got what you need you got to try
me I know I got what you need you got to
try me
bring that body
closer I want to feel your skin up on
mine like I already know you I'm
grabbing from behind as we
wine I got CH down my spine as we
wine girl we might be meant to be try in
the morning when the sun comes rising up
try me in the afternoon but you just
can't get enough
I satisfaction guarantee yeah I got what
you need you got to try
me I got what you need you I try me
[Music]
right you try me
baby for all my go yeah go yeah goo yeah
for all my gos go yeah go yeah go yeah
yeah yeah want slow for your boy
[Music]